<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ruby on Rails on Klimo.io</title>
    <link>/tags/ruby-on-rails/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ruby on Rails on Klimo.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Jan Klimo</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/ruby-on-rails/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Robin PRO Image Gallery</title>
      <link>/shopify-apps/robin-pro-image-gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/shopify-apps/robin-pro-image-gallery/</guid>
      <description>Robin PRO is the definitive image gallery app built for 2019. Fast, mobile-first, beautiful. A must-have for any shop owner who cares about details and pixel-perfect user experience. Create a great first impression that converts into sales!   Ready to take your store to the next level? Install Robin PRO  Why You&amp;rsquo;ll Love Robin PRO Image Gallery Image gallery app built for 2019 Fast, mobile-first, beautiful. Create a great first impression that converts into sales!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seeding Images From Unsplash</title>
      <link>/posts/unsplash-seeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/unsplash-seeds/</guid>
      <description>Recently we&amp;rsquo;ve been making a more conscious effort to improve the quality of our seed data.
Firstly, to make it easier to onboard new team members. Secondly, to make the app ready for Review Apps. Certainly, it&amp;rsquo;s a great thing to be able to just re-seed your database if your local experiments go awry 😅
The kind of seeds I&amp;rsquo;ve seen over the years typically neglect images. They either use a minimal placeholder, use a few nicer images that are repeated over and over and checked into source control, or don&amp;rsquo;t do anything at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Your App&#39;s MRR?</title>
      <link>/posts/what-is-your-apps-mrr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/what-is-your-apps-mrr/</guid>
      <description>One of the most useful features I&amp;rsquo;d love to see Shopify add to the Partners portal is a chart of your MRR (monthly recurring revenue).
This answers a simple question of What is the current value of all of my active recurring charges? In other words, how much money will you receive in the next 30 days?
There is one problem with the Earnings chart:
It&amp;rsquo;s a lagging indicator showing you the last 30 days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating AWS Workflows</title>
      <link>/posts/automating-aws-workflows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/automating-aws-workflows/</guid>
      <description>This article shows you how to use AWS CLI programmatically to automate your deployment process. We&amp;rsquo;ll upload assets to S3 (specifying their ACL and caching behavior) and invalidate CloudFront cache. Starting with a local shell script, we conclude with plugging the script into our CircleCI workflow. It may be especially useful if you&amp;rsquo;re using Rails with Webpacker, but no experience with Rails is required.
 My latest Shopify app Robin PRO renders image galleries on customer stores.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>